  import 'package:Gem_Quest/quiz.dart';

  List<QuizQuestion> easyQuestions = [
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the hardest gemstone?',
      answers: ['Ruby', 'Diamond', 'Sapphire', 'Emerald'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is known for its deep red color?',
      answers: ['Ruby', 'Diamond', 'Topaz', 'Amethyst'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What color is a sapphire most commonly associated with?',
      answers: ['Green', 'Blue', 'Yellow', 'Red'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What gemstone is known as the "stone of love"?',
      answers: ['Opal', 'Diamond', 'Ruby', 'Emerald'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 1,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is the birthstone for May?',
      answers: ['Emerald', 'Amethyst', 'Peridot', 'Sapphire'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is formed from fossilized tree resin?',
      answers: ['Amber', 'Citrine', 'Aquamarine', 'Garnet'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What gemstone is typically green and associated with wealth?',
      answers: ['Emerald', 'Ruby', 'Sapphire', 'Opal'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone changes color under different lighting?',
      answers: ['Alexandrite', 'Topaz', 'Moonstone', 'Tourmaline'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'What is the primary component of a diamond?',
      answers: ['Carbon', 'Quartz', 'Silicon', 'Oxygen'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
    QuizQuestion(
      question: 'Which gemstone is known for its iridescent play of colors?',
      answers: ['Opal', 'Citrine', 'Amber', 'Aquamarine'],
      correctAnswerIndex: 0,
    ),
  ];
